<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-08-30T12:47:25-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">CIT 480 BLOG</title><subtitle>CIT WEEKLY BLOGS.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Docker Install</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/08/29/docker-install.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Docker Install" /><published>2019-08-29T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-08-29T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/08/29/docker-install</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/08/29/docker-install.html">&lt;p&gt;To download docker you need to make an account with Docker. 
The instructions provided by the lab offers several links for downloading docker depending on your OS. 
I personally used Option 4: Windows 10 Home Edition 
When clicking on the link provided the instructions to download docker are pretty straight forward. They provide information on different windows versions as well, images are also helpful. Maybe a few more images would be helpful of the other setup pages would be helpful as to setting up docker the way it is required for CIT160. Also the document could also provide help for issues commonly faced by first-time users.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">To download docker you need to make an account with Docker. The instructions provided by the lab offers several links for downloading docker depending on your OS. I personally used Option 4: Windows 10 Home Edition When clicking on the link provided the instructions to download docker are pretty straight forward. They provide information on different windows versions as well, images are also helpful. Maybe a few more images would be helpful of the other setup pages would be helpful as to setting up docker the way it is required for CIT160. Also the document could also provide help for issues commonly faced by first-time users.</summary></entry></feed>